

# Yogamoorthy Mohan

••••••••Visual Designer



+91 99621 71077



yogamoorthy.mohan@gmail.com



#13, AI, Block, Visalakshi Garden, Mylapore, Chennai - 600 004.

#### **About Me**

Hi I am Yogamoorthy Mohan, from Chennai working as a Graphic Designer past 12years!! I have been working as a professional "pre-press designer", and have always been loving my work as a designer and I am a thirsty person to learn new designing and creative art work. I have specialized on projects like Photo Manipulation, Concept Creation,Infographic, Magazine Design, Medical & Vector illustrations.

### **Educational qualifications**

#### **Higher Secondary**

Corporation higher secondary school Year: 2000-2002

#### B.Com

Madras University Year: 2002-2005

#### Multimedia

Institute: Sun Software in Mandaveli, Chennai

Year: October 2004

## **Professional experience**

Organization: **India Cement Pvt. Ltd** Designation: Graphic designer

Team: Corporate (House Journals/Annual Reports / Policy Manuals/ Corporate Films)

Duration: June 2005 to 2013

Organization: **2adpro Media Solution Pvt. Ltd**Designation: Creative Executive designer

Duration: 2013 to 2014

Organization: India Cement Pvt. Ltd

Freelancing Designer Duration: 2016 to 2019

Organization: Paragon Digital Services

Designation: Visual Designer
Duration: 2019 to till working
Work for Switzerland based clients and
Handling a design team, report to the
Creative manager. Pitching fresh and
innovative ideas to clients and also
collaborating with the **AMAZON** project
supporting the team. Hands-on experience

with Adobe Suite.

## **Technical skills**















